Hello,
Здравствуйте
I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky. Where are you from?
Я из города Хмельницкий Вы откуда
I’m from Nizhny Novgorod, it’s a cool
Я из Нижнего Новгорода прикольно
musician, I’m
музыкант
just learning, I
только учусь
can assemble something, I
могу собирать что-нибудь
don’t need to, but I’m discussing what to
не надо а что обсуждать
discuss. Today we saw a video of
обсуждаю Сегодня видели видео как сын
Ramzan Kadyrov’s son beating a Russian guy
Рамзана Кадырова избивает русского парня
in a pre-trial detention center in Chechnya.
в СИЗО Чечни
Yes. Do you think he’ll
да Как вы считаете
most likely not go to jail? You
скорее всего не сядет
can beat a Russian  it would just be
можно русского бить просто будут
possible to blow up
можно было взрывать
That's exactly what the investigation still has
Вот именно то что следствие до сих пор
n't established Oles Buzina excursions
не установил Олесь Бузина экскурсии
something was actually a fictional character
что-то вообще был вымышленный персонаж
we had these were real people
у нас были эти были реальные человек
what a real bald so
какой реальный лысый такой
bald so yes This is a dude What are you chasing?
лысый такой да Это чувак Ты что гонишь У
We have writers brothers Kapranova  they
нас есть писатели братья капранова они
wrote a book And there is a literary
написали книжку Да и там литературный
hero Ales Elder they specifically
герой Алесь бузины они Вот специально по
named it comically and in order to
комически назвали и для того чтобы
promote this book they took an actor
пиарить эту книжку они взяли актера
who walked around and introduced himself as Les
который ходил и представлялся лесем
Elder there was no such journalist why they
бузино не было такого журналиста зачем
blew him up they blew them up according to the book
его взорвали они взорвали у них по книге
you read the book of the Kapranov brothers  this is
ты читал книгу братьев капрановых это
how the book will end wrong they
так книга сюжет закончится не так
did it like they wrote everything There was
сделали вроде как написали все Не было
no forest there will be an
никакого леса будет
actor
актер был
Ivan tell me who he is
Иван скажи кто такой
Listen Okay good good
Слушай Ладно хорошо хорошо
oh they did the character of the Kapranov brothers
ой сделали персонаж братьев капрановых
again Ivanka Who is Oles Buzina
еще раз Иванка Кто такой Олесь Бузина
Alisa who is Oles Buzina
Алиса кто такой Олесь Бузина
Alisa who is Olesya Buzina Ukraine
Алиса кто такой Олеся бузина Украина по
nothing was found according to your request
вашему запросу ничего не нашлось
Now look again Ivanka Alice
Вот теперь смотри еще раз Иванка Алиса
didn’t find anything after going through the elderberry And you
ничего не нашла пролеся бузину А ты
tell me Ivanka Who is the lesbian
скажи Иванка Кто такая лесбузина
fictional character of the Kapranov brothers
вымышленный персонаж братьев капрановых
once again a journalist
еще раз журналист
Unfortunately nothing was found
К сожалению ничего найти не получилось
just In short, listen again this was the
просто Короче слушай еще раз вот это был
Kapranov brothers wrote  they
вот братья капрановые написали книгу они
made a book about Oles Buzin, they took this actor,
сделали Олесь Бузина взяли этого актера
he was so flinty and bald in our Les Kurbas theater,
он в театре Леся Курбаса у нас такой
they
кременный и лысый такой они его
brought him to a press conference of some kind, it seemed
приводили на пресс-конференции какие-то
like he introduced himself to Elder Forest
вроде он представлялся лес бузина
on purpose, he was presenting something there, he was
специально там что-то представлял
cursing, it seemed like everything was then based on his book on
ругался вроде все потом по книге его
May 2  house of trade unions Ukraine
2 мая дом Профсоюзов Украина
[laughter]
[смех]
[music]
[музыка]
Ivanka is not you Formulate it completely
Иванка не ты Сформулируй полностью
Ivanka What happened on May 2 in the house of
Иванка Что произошло 2 мая в доме
trade unions
профсоюзов
Odessa And in the city of Odessa everything is now
Одессу А в городе Одессе все теперь
clear because well, we need to remove something;
понятно потому что ну надо что-то снять
we were smarter than Alice, but we also need to clarify
было наш умнее Алисы но надо и уточнять
in what year  it means May 2 is the House of
тоже В каком году значит 2 мая дом
Trade Unions,
профсоюзов
you can ask this out loud too, yes
ты можешь это задать тоже вслух да
Once again like this
Еще раз так
Ivanka Ivanochka Sanochka Say please
Иванка иваночка саночка Скажи пожалуйста
Excuse me I’m in Russian Dana damn it’s necessary
Извинишь Я на русском Дана блин нужно
for a Russian Say please in
для россиянина Скажи пожалуйста на
Russian Answer what happened on May 2
русском языке Ответь что случилось 2 мая
in Odessa in the House of Trade Unions
в Одессе в доме профсоюзов
[laughter]
[смех]
[music]
[музыка]
Tsar Bingo I just don’t know I’m a fish in a
царь Бинго просто я не знаю я вот рыба в
stick for salads
стике на салоты
I know damn it Write in the comments
Я знаю блин вот Напишите в комментариях
what you think It’s
что вы думаете
just that I’m a dad
Просто ну я папаша
stupidly in short they let me out to test it
тупо короче выпустили испытать
just
просто
Let’s ask I woke up I can’t find I thought
Спросим пробудила не могу найти Я думала
she was infecting
она заражать
just that’s why all Ukrainians were
просто поэтому всему украинцам было
honest it was an honest like  for the mood Yes,
честно было честный лайк для настроя Да
we can be a couple because we are reasonable,
мы паре можем потому что мы разумничать
we are also reasonable Slava Ukraine
мы тоже разум Слава Украины
damn
блин
kilogram right at a time autumn
килограмм прям за раз осень
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube driving us through the Georgiev car into a
YouTube загоняя нас через кар Георгиев в
shadow ban and a very rich look is not
теневый бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown in order
показывается информация про стримы тому
to  little operational little animal
для того чтобы мало оперативный зверезок
Sign right at a time and try there in a
Подпишите прям за раз а попыт там в
kilogram about Cream video
килограмме о Крим видео
information and we are with you on stylish
информация и мы с вами по стильной
operational stars
оперативной звездок
Total type we will show you YouTube Glory to
Итого типа покажем вам YouTube Слава
Ukraine
Украине